President, Office of the; Records ua000
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Office of Vincent O'Leary Records, 1960-1998; 12; 118 cubic ft.
  - New Faculty/Staff, 1984-1985 (Box 58, Folder 23)
  - NYS Legislature, 1986-1987 (Box 58, Folder 24)
  - NYS Legislature, 1985 (Box 58, Folder 25)
  - Parking Policy, 1985-1987 (Box 58, Folder 26)
  - Performance Programs, 1986-1987 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Performance Programs, 1985-1986 (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - Performance Programs, 1984-1985 (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Personnel, 1986-1987 (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - Personnel, 1985 (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - Planning, 1986-1987 (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - Planning, 1984-1985 (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - Planning- Leif's NCHEMS Paper, Undated (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - Plant, 1986-1987 (Box 59, Folder 9)
  - Plant, 1980-1982 (Box 59, Folder 10)
  - Presidential Scholars Program, 1987 (Box 59, Folder 11)
  - Programs & Priorities, 1986 (Box 59, Folder 12)
  - Programs & Priorities, 1985 (Box 59, Folder 13)
  - Programs & Priorities, 1984 (Box 59, Folder 14)
  - Public Safety, 1986-1987 (Box 59, Folder 15)
  - Public Service, 1986-1987 (Box 59, Folder 16)
  - Purple & Gold, 1986-1987 (Box 59, Folder 17)
  - Purple & Gold, 1982-1985 (Box 59, Folder 18)
  - Racism, 1986 (Box 59, Folder 19)
  - Racism, 1983-1984 (Box 59, Folder 20)
  - Racism, 1982 (Box 59, Folder 21)
  - Registrar, 1983-1987 (Box 59, Folder 22)
  - Registrar, 1981-1982 (Box 59, Folder 23)
  - Salaries, 1986-1987 (Box 59, Folder 24)
  - Salaries, 1984-1985 (Box 59, Folder 25)
  - State Education Department, 1986-1987 (Box 59, Folder 26)
  - State Education Department, 1984-1985 (Box 59, Folder 27)
  - SED: Advisory Council on Postsecondary Advisory Council Ed, 1986-1987 (Box 59, Folder 28)
  - SED: Advisory Council on Postsecondary Advisory Education, 1985 (Box 59, Folder 29)
  - SED: Commissioner's Regulations, 1986-1987 (Box 59, Folder 30)
  - Student Association, 1987 (Box 59, Folder 31)
  - Student Association, 1986 (Box 59, Folder 32)
  - Student Association, 1985 (Box 59, Folder 33)
  - Telephone Systems, 1986-1987 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Telephone Systems, 1984-1985 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Undergraduate Studies, 1986-1987 (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - Undergraduate Studies, 1983-1985 (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - United Way, 1985-1987 (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - University Auxiliary Services, 1986-1987 (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - University Auxiliary Services, 1983-1985 (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - University Centers, 1986-1987 (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - University Centers, 1985 (Box 60, Folder 9)
  - University Foundation, 1986-1987 (Box 60, Folder 10)
  - University Foundation, 1985 (Box 60, Folder 11)
  - University of Albany Fund, 1987 (Box 60, Folder 12)
  - University of Albany Fund, 1985-1987 (Box 60, Folder 13)
  - University Relations, 1987 (Box 60, Folder 14)
  - University Relations, 1986 (Box 60, Folder 15)
  - World Week, 1985 (Box 60, Folder 16)
  - Writers Institute, 1984-1987 (Box 60, Folder 17)
  - ACUSNY, 1987 (Box 60, Folder 18)
  - ACUSNY, 1985 (Box 60, Folder 19)
  - Hudson-Mohawk Association, 1987 (Box 60, Folder 20)
  - Hudson-Mohawk Association, 1983-1986 (Box 60, Folder 21)
  - UUP, 1987 (Box 60, Folder 22)
  - UUP, 1985 (Box 60, Folder 23)
  - Planning Instructions, General Planning Information, 1989; 1988; 1987-1988; 1987; 1985-1986 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - School of Business, 1990; 1989; 1988; 1987 (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - School of Education, 1990; 1989; 1988; 1987 (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - College of Humanities and Fine Arts, 1990; 1989; 1988; 1987; 1985 (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - School of Public Health, 1990; 1989; 1988; 1987 (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - College of Science and Mathematics, 1990; 1989; 1988; 1987 (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Rockefeller College, 1990; 1989; 1988; 1987 (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - School of Criminal Justice, 1990; 1989; 1988; 1987 (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - School of Information Science and Policy, 1990; 1989; 1988; 1987 (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - Graduate School of Public Affairs, 1990; 1989; 1988; 1987 (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - Center for Women in Government, 1988 (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - School of Social Welfare, 1985-1990 (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Ringel Institute, 1988; 1986 (Box 63, Folder 9)
  - College of Social and Behavioral Sciences, 1990; 1989; 1988; 1987 (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - Planning Instructions, General Planning Information, 1990; 1989; 1988; 1987 (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - Academic Affairs, 1990; 1989; 1988; 1987 (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - Information Systems and Libraries, 1990; 1989; 1988; 1987 (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - Finance and Business, 1990; 1989; 1988; 1987 (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - President's Areas, Undated (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - Affirmative Action, 1990; 1989; 1988; 1987 (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - Institutional Research, 1990; 1989; 1988; 1987 (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - Research and Graduate Studies, 1990; 1989; 1988; 1987 (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - Student Affairs, 1990; 1989; 1988; 1987 (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - University Advancement, 1990; 1989 (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - Development and Alumni Affairs, 1989; 1988; 1987 (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - University Affairs, 1989; 1988; 1987 (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - Ad Hoc University Centers Committee, 1980-1982 (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - Admission of Ex-Offenders Committee, 1980-1981 (Box 69, Folder 2)
  - Classification and Compensation Committee, 1986-1987 (Box 69, Folder 3)
  - Collective Bargaining Committee, 1981-1989 (Box 69, Folder 4)
  - Residence Hall Committee, 1981 (Box 69, Folder 5)
  - Telecommunications Committee, 1981-1984 (Box 69, Folder 6)
  - Albany/Colonie Chamber of Commerce, 1985 February 28 (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - Albany High School Graduation, 1980 June 22 (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Albany Rotary Club, 1983 November 10 (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - Albany Rotary Club, Albany Thruway House, 1980 October 30 (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - Albany School District Annual Meeting, 1979 September 4 (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - Albany Sons of St. Patrick, Albany Thruway House, 1981 March 17 (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - American Society of Criminology, Washington, D.C, 1981 November 11 (Box 70, Folder 7)
  - Association of College Unions-- Remark, 1978 October 14 (Box 70, Folder 8)
  - Bethlehem Chamber of Commerce, Normanside Country Club, 1980 March 27 (Box 70, Folder 9)
  - B'nai B'rith Covenant Award Breakfast, 1982 January 24 (Box 70, Folder 10)
  - Campus Awareness Day, CC Fountain Area, 1978 April 19 (Box 70, Folder 11)
  - Capital Partnership Recognition Dinner, 1978 October 26 (Box 70, Folder 12)
  - Columbia-Greene Community College Honors Program, 1982 April 28 (Box 70, Folder 13)
  - Correctional Education Association, Costa Mesa, CA, 1981 July 5 (Box 70, Folder 14)
  - Council on Social Work Education, Boston, 1979 March 6 (Box 70, Folder 15)
  - Education Faculty Meeting, 1979 September 7 (Box 70, Folder 16)
  - Executive Committee on Sentencing, 1978 November 16 (Box 70, Folder 17)
  - Governor's Conference on Families, 1980 January 12 (Box 70, Folder 18)
  - Governor's Task Force on Equity and Excellence in Education, 1979 September 26 (Box 70, Folder 19)
  - Heritage Day, St. Peter's Church, 1988 May 1 (Box 70, Folder 20)
  - Hope House Dinner, Century House, Latham, 1980 October 22 (Box 70, Folder 21)
  - Inaugural Remarks, CC Ballroom, 1978 October 7 (Box 70, Folder 22)
  - Institute of Internal Auditors, "White Collar Criminals", 1978 December 14 (Box 70, Folder 23)
  - Jewish Students Coalition Rally, 1978 April 25 (Box 70, Folder 24)
  - Kiwanis Clu, 1978 December 5 (Box 70, Folder 25)
  - Martin Luther King Memorial, 1980 January 15 (Box 70, Folder 26)
  - Middle Atlantic States Correctional Association, Undated (Box 70, Folder 27)
  - National Alliance of Businessmen, Thruway House, 1978 November 16 (Box 70, Folder 28)
  - National Conference on Sentencing, Baltimore, MD, 1984 January 18 (Box 70, Folder 29)
  - National Parole Symposium, University of Maryland, 1980 April 9 (Box 70, Folder 30)
  - NYS Police Graduation, 1982 March 26 (Box 70, Folder 31)
  - NYS Secondary School Student Organization, Welcoming Remarks, 1978 January 5 (Box 70, Folder 32)
  - Philosophy Forum, Russell Sag, 1981 February 10 (Box 70, Folder 33)
  - Public Personnel Administration Conference, 1982 October 18 (Box 70, Folder 34)
  - Remarks to the Faculty, 1990 May 9 (Box 70, Folder 35)
  - Remarks to the Faculty, 1989 September 14 (Box 70, Folder 36)
  - Spring Faculty Meeting, 1989 May 10 (Box 70, Folder 37)
  - Remarks to the Faculty, 1988 September 14 (Box 70, Folder 38)
  - Remarks to the Faculty, 1988 May 6 (Box 70, Folder 39)
  - Remarks to the Faculty, 1987 September 16 (Box 70, Folder 40)
  - Remarks to the Faculty, 1987 September 16 (Box 70, Folder 41)
  - Remarks to the Faculty, 1987 (Box 70, Folder 42)
  - Remarks to the Faculty, 1986 September 12 (Box 70, Folder 43)
  - Remarks to the Faculty, 1986 (Box 70, Folder 44)
  - Remarks to the Faculty, 1985 September 11 (Box 70, Folder 45)
  - Remarks to the Faculty, 1985 (Box 70, Folder 46)
  - Remarks to the Faculty, 1984 September 12 (Box 70, Folder 47)
  - Remarks to the Faculty, 1984 May 4 (Box 70, Folder 48)
  - Remarks to the Faculty, 1983 September (Box 70, Folder 49)
  - Remarks to the Faculty, 1983 May 4 (Box 70, Folder 50)
  - Remarks to the Faculty, 1982 September 9 (Box 70, Folder 51)
  - Remarks to the Faculty, 1982 May 6 (Box 70, Folder 52)
  - Remarks to the Faculty, 1981 September 9 (Box 70, Folder 53)
  - Remarks to the Faculty, 1981 May 5 (Box 70, Folder 54)
  - Remarks to the Faculty, 1980 September 10 (Box 70, Folder 55)
  - Remarks to the Faculty, 1980 May 7 (Box 70, Folder 56)
  - Remarks to the Faculty, CC Ballroom, 1979 September 5 (Box 70, Folder 57)
  - Remarks to the Faculty, CC Ballroom, 1979 May 3 (Box 70, Folder 58)
  - Remarks to the Faculty, LC 18, 1978 September 6 (Box 70, Folder 59)
  - Remarks to the Faculty - Spring, 1978 (Box 70, Folder 60)
  - Remarks to the Faculty, CC Ballroom, 1977 September 1 (Box 70, Folder 61)
  - Residence Staff Orientation, 1978 August 21 (Box 70, Folder 62)
  - Russell Sage, Kah1 Retirement, Undated (Box 70, Folder 63)
  - State Academy for Public Administration, Welcoming Remark, 1977 October 19 (Box 70, Folder 64)
  - Soviet Dissident Day, 1980 March 25 (Box 70, Folder 65)
  - SUNY A Faculty Wives, 1979 March 24 (Box 70, Folder 66)
  - Swyer Memorial, 1989 April 5 (Box 70, Folder 67)
  - Testimony- Joint Legis Commission on Science & Technology, 1986 April 12 (Box 70, Folder 68)
  - Vanderbilt University: Public Policy Series, 1989 September 30 (Box 70, Folder 69)
  - World Week, 1985 March 5 (Box 70, Folder 70)
  - Commission on the Administration of Justice- Final Report, Undated (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - Congratulatory Letters, Undated (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - O'Leary: Congratulatory Letters, Undated (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - 78 Pres. Appointment, Undated (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - O'Leary: Congratulatory Letters, Undated (Box 71, Folder 5)
  - 77 Pres. Appointment, Undated (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - Strategic Plan Albany Schools, Undated (Box 71, Folder 7)
  - Tree of Life Award, Undated (Box 71, Folder 8)
  - University Club Material, Undated (Box 71, Folder 9)
  - Albany Cultural/Educational Task Force, Undated (Box 71, Folder 10)
  - Capital Leadership Steering Committee, Undated (Box 71, Folder 11)
  - The Fifty Group, Undated (Box 71, Folder 12)
  - Mayor's Advisory Committee on Downtown Albany, Undated (Box 71, Folder 13)
  - Mayor's Constitution Commission, Undated (Box 71, Folder 14)
  - Mayor's Strategic Planning Committee, Undated (Box 71, Folder 15)
  - Recommendations A-B, Undated (Box 71, Folder 16)
  - Recommendations C-D, Undated (Box 71, Folder 17)
  - Recommendations E-G, Undated (Box 71, Folder 18)
  - Recommendations H-J, Undated (Box 71, Folder 19)
  - Recommendations K-M, Undated (Box 71, Folder 20)
  - Recommendations N-P, Undated (Box 71, Folder 21)
  - Recommendations Q-S, Undated (Box 71, Folder 22)
  - Recommendations T-V, Undated (Box 71, Folder 23)
  - Recommendations W-Z, Undated (Box 71, Folder 24)
  - Committee Files, Undated (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Academic Policy Group (APG), 1987 (Box 73, Folder 1)
  - Assessment, 1987 (Box 73, Folder 2)
  - Budget Hearing, 1988-1989 (Box 73, Folder 3)
  - Budget Panel, 1987 (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - Capital Budget, 1987-1988 (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - Challenge and the Choice, 1987 (Box 73, Folder 6)
  - Challenge and the Choice, 1988 (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - Challenge and Choice Campus Input, 1988 (Box 73, Folder 8)
  - Challenge and Choice Working Drafts, 1988 (Box 73, Folder 9)
  - Enrollment- Minority, 1987 (Box 73, Folder 10)
  - Enrollment- Minority, 1987 (Box 73, Folder 11)
  - Enrollment Goals/Plan, 1987 (Box 73, Folder 12)
  - Enrollment Management, 1987 (Box 73, Folder 13)
  - Enrollment Management Committee, 1987 (Box 73, Folder 14)
  - Enrollment Plan (Revenue), 1987 (Box 73, Folder 15)
  - Fall Management Conference, 1987 (Box 73, Folder 16)
  - Future Survey, 1987 (Box 73, Folder 17)
  - Institutional Research, 1985-1986 (Box 73, Folder 18)
  - Institutional Research, 1987 (Box 73, Folder 19)
  - Long Range Planning Committee, 1987 (Box 73, Folder 20)
  - President's Management Committee (PMC) Meeting Minutes, 1987 (Box 73, Folder 21)
  - Programs and Priorities, 1987 (Box 73, Folder 22)
  - Programs and Priorities, 1989 (Box 73, Folder 23)
  - Retention, 1987 (Box 73, Folder 24)
  - Work Plans for Major Responsibilities- RBH, 1988-1989 (Box 73, Folder 25)
  - Readings from Ronald Hoskins' Class POS 416Y/516, 1990 (Box 73, Folder 26)
  - Academic Affairs Five-Year Plan, 1988-1989 (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - Academic Affairs Five-Year Plan Progress Report, 1989-1990 (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - Division of Finance and Business Five-Year Perspective, 1990 May (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - Affirmative Action Office Five-Year Plan 1990-1995, 1990 May (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - Office of Institutional Research Five-Year Plan 1990-1994, 1990 May (Box 74, Folder 5)
  - Division of Research and Graduate Studies Five-Year Plan Update, 1989 (Box 74, Folder 6)
  - Division of Student Affairs Five-Year Plan for 1989-1994, 1989 May (Box 74, Folder 7)
  - Information Systems and Technology Five-Year Plan, 1988-1993 (Box 74, Folder 8)
  - First Annual Update, 1989 February (Box 74, Folder 9)
  - Information Systems and Technology Five-Year Plans, 1988 May (Box 74, Folder 10)
  - Division of University Advancement Five-Year Plan, 1990-1994 (Box 74, Folder 11)
  - Division of University Advancement Five-Year Plan, 1990-1994 (Box 74, Folder 12)
  - School of Business Five-Year Plan 1988-89 to 1992-93, 1988 July (Box 74, Folder 13)
  - School of Education Five-Year Plan, 1990-1994 (Box 74, Folder 14)
  - School of Education Progress Report, 1989-1990 (Box 74, Folder 15)
  - Empire State Youth Theatre Institute, A Strategic Plan, 1989-1993 (Box 74, Folder 16)
  - College of Humanities and Fine Arts Five-Year Plan, 1988-1993 (Box 74, Folder 17)
  - College of Humanities and Fine Arts Departmental Progress Report, 1989-1990 (Box 74, Folder 18)
  - College of Humanities and Fine Arts, Departmental Progress Report, 1989-1990 (Box 74, Folder 19)
  - School of Public Health - Progress Report, 1988-1989 (Box 74, Folder 20)
  - School of Public Health Five-Year Plan, 1990-1994 (Box 74, Folder 21)
  - The Nelson A. Rockefeller College of Public Affairs and Policy Progress Report, 1987-1988 (Box 74, Folder 22)
  - The Nelson A. Rockefeller College of Public Affairs and Policy Five-Year Plan, 1990-1994 (Box 74, Folder 23)
  - The Nelson A. Rockefeller College of Public Affairs and Policy Five-Year Plan, 1987-1992 (Box 74, Folder 24)
  - College of Science and Mathematics Five-Year Plan, 1989 August (Box 74, Folder 25)
  - College of Science and Mathematics Five-Year Plan First Progress Report, 1990 June (Box 74, Folder 26)
  - College of Social and Behavioral Sciences Five-Year Plan, 1990-1995 (Box 74, Folder 27)
  - College of Social and Behavioral Sciences Five-Year Plan Update, 1998 August (Box 74, Folder 28)
  - Yugoslavia, Undated (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - Middle States Periodic Report, 1986-1987 (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Middle States Evaluation- Institutional Response, Undated (Box 75, Folder 3)
  - Middle States Accreditation 1980- Evaluation Team Report, Undated (Box 75, Folder 4)
  - Middle States Accreditation 1980- Self-Study Document, Undated (Box 75, Folder 5)
  - Middle States Accreditation, 1980 (Box 75, Folder 6)
  - Middle States Accreditation, 1979 (Box 75, Folder 7)
  - Middle States Accreditation, 1978 (Box 75, Folder 8)
  - Middle States Steering Committee, 1979-1980 (Box 75, Folder 9)
  - Middle States Accreditation Visit- Expenses, 1980 December (Box 75, Folder 10)
  - Middle States, Undated (Box 75, Folder 11)
  - Middle States Accreditation 1971- SUNYA Response, 1973 (Box 75, Folder 12)
  - Middle States Accreditation 1971- Evaluation Team Report, Undated (Box 75, Folder 13)
  - Middle States Accreditation 1971- Self-Study Report, Undated (Box 75, Folder 14)
  - Middle States Accreditation, 1969-1973 (Box 75, Folder 15)
  - ACE, 1988 (Box 75, Folder 16)
  - American Council on Education, Undated (Box 75, Folder 17)
  - ACUSNY, 1988 (Box 75, Folder 18)
  - ACMCT (Assn. of Council Members and College Trustees of SUNY), Undated (Box 75, Folder 19)
  - CSEA, Undated (Box 75, Folder 20)
  - Hudson-Mohawk Association, 1989 (Box 75, Folder 21)
  - Hudson-Mohawk Association, 1988 (Box 75, Folder 22)
  - National Alliance of Business, Undated (Box 75, Folder 23)
  - UUP, 1989 (Box 75, Folder 24)
  - UUP, 1988 (Box 75, Folder 25)
  - Wessell Commission- 3 folders, Undated (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - EBF Statement to the Commission, Undated (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - Management Conference, Undated (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - Manila Initiative, Undated (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - Mayor, 1989-1990 (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - Meeting Matrix, Undated (Box 76, Folder 6)
  - New Faculty/Prof. Staff, 1989 (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - Reception for New and Returning Women, Undated (Box 76, Folder 8)
  - New Faculty/Staff, 1988 (Box 76, Folder 9)
  - N.Y.S. Research University Consortium, Undated (Box 76, Folder 10)
  - N.Y.S. Legislature, 1989 (Box 76, Folder 11)
  - N.Y.S. Legislature, 1988 (Box 76, Folder 12)
  - Office of Employee Relations, Undated (Box 76, Folder 13)
  - Parking Policy, 1989 (Box 76, Folder 14)
  - Parking Policy, 1988 (Box 76, Folder 15)
  - Performance Programs, 1989-1990 (Box 76, Folder 16)
  - Performance Programs, 1988-1989 (Box 76, Folder 17)
  - Performance Programs, 1987-1988 (Box 76, Folder 18)
  - Personal Service Regular Management (PSR), Undated (Box 76, Folder 19)
  - Personnel, 1989 (Box 76, Folder 20)
  - Personnel, 1988 (Box 76, Folder 21)
  - Presidential and Frederick Douglass Scholars, 1989 (Box 76, Folder 22)
  - Presidential Scholars Program, 1988 (Box 76, Folder 23)
  - Programs and Priorities, Undated (Box 76, Folder 24)
  - Public Safety, 1989 (Box 76, Folder 25)
  - Public Safety, 1988 (Box 76, Folder 26)
  - Public Service, 1989 (Box 76, Folder 27)
  - Public Service, 1988 (Box 76, Folder 28)
  - Quality of Student Life, Undated (Box 76, Folder 29)
  - RPI, Undated (Box 76, Folder 30)
  - RPI Center, Undated (Box 76, Folder 31)
  - Resource Management Committee, Undated (Box 76, Folder 32)
  - Resource Development, Undated (Box 76, Folder 33)
  - Board of Trustees, 1971 (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - Board of Trustees, 1972 (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - Board of Trustees, 1973 (Box 77, Folder 3)
  - Board of Trustees, 1974 (Box 77, Folder 4)
  - Board of Trustees, 1975 (Box 77, Folder 5)
  - Board of Trustees, 1976 (Box 77, Folder 6)
  - Board of Trustees, 1977 (Box 77, Folder 7)
  - Board of Trustees, 1978 (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - Board of Trustees, 1979 (Box 77, Folder 9)
  - Board of Trustees, 1980 (Box 77, Folder 10)
  - Board of Trustees, 1981 (Box 77, Folder 11)
  - Board of Trustees, 1982 (Box 77, Folder 12)
  - Board of Trustees, 1983 (Box 77, Folder 13)
  - Board of Trustees, 1984 (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Board of Trustees, 1985 (Box 77, Folder 15)
  - Board of Trustees, 1965-1975 (Box 77, Folder 16)
  - Board of Trustees, 1976 (Box 77, Folder 17)
  - Board of Trustees, 1977 (Box 77, Folder 18)
  - Board of Trustees, 1978 (Box 77, Folder 19)
  - Board of Trustees, 1979 (Box 77, Folder 20)
  - Board of Trustees, 1980 (Box 77, Folder 21)
  - Board of Trustees, 1981 (Box 77, Folder 22)
  - Board of Trustees, 1982 (Box 77, Folder 23)
  - Board of Trustees, 1983 (Box 77, Folder 24)
  - Board of Trustees, 1984 (Box 77, Folder 25)
  - Board of Trustees, 1985 (Box 77, Folder 26)
  - University Council, 1982 (Box 77, Folder 27)
  - University Council, 1983 (Box 77, Folder 28)
  - University Council, 1984 (Box 77, Folder 29)
  - University Council, 1985 (Box 77, Folder 30)
  - Academic Calendar- Other Colleges, Undated (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - Accreditation Letters, Undated (Box 78, Folder 2)
  - Administrative Systems Development, Undated (Box 78, Folder 3)
  - Admission of Ex-Offenders, Undated (Box 78, Folder 4)
  - Admission- Transfer Agreement, Undated (Box 78, Folder 5)
  - Adoption of Rules, Undated (Box 78, Folder 6)
  - Assembly Hall, Undated (Box 78, Folder 7)
  - Belgrade Exchange, Undated (Box 78, Folder 8)
  - Brazil Exchange, Undated (Box 78, Folder 9)
  - Buildings/Construction, Undated (Box 78, Folder 10)
  - Campaign, 1994 (Box 78, Folder 11)
  - Capital City Renaissance Corporation, 1989 (Box 78, Folder 12)
  - "Carillon Committee", Undated (Box 78, Folder 13)
  - Capital Region Consortium of SUNY, 1988 (Box 78, Folder 14)
  - Chapel House/Campus Ministry, 1988-1989 (Box 78, Folder 15)
  - China Exchange- Exchange Agreements, Undated (Box 78, Folder 16)
  - Committee on Future Priorities and Missions, 1987 (Box 78, Folder 17)
  - Community Affairs Management Committee, Undated (Box 78, Folder 18)
  - Educational Assessment, Undated (Box 78, Folder 19)
  - Enrollment/Revenue Problem, Undated (Box 78, Folder 20)
  - Extramural Activity, Undated (Box 78, Folder 21)
  - HESC Presidents Committee, Undated (Box 78, Folder 22)
  - Hungary/Poland, Undated (Box 78, Folder 23)
  - Indonesia Project, Undated (Box 78, Folder 24)
  - Internal Audit, 1989 (Box 78, Folder 25)
  - Internal Audit, 1988 (Box 78, Folder 26)
  - Internal Control, Undated (Box 78, Folder 27)
  - Library, 1989 (Box 78, Folder 28)
  - Library, 1988 (Box 78, Folder 29)
  - Liberty Partnerships, 1989 (Box 78, Folder 30)
  - MACCC Background Materials, Undated (Box 78, Folder 31)
  - Sexuality Week, Undated (Box 79, Folder 1)
  - Sloan Commission, Undated (Box 79, Folder 2)
  - Special Olympics, Undated (Box 79, Folder 3)
  - State Education Department, 1989 (Box 79, Folder 4)
  - State Education Department, 1988 (Box 79, Folder 5)
  - S.E.D.: Einstein/Schweitzer-Chairs, Undated (Box 79, Folder 6)
  - S.E.D.: Tentative State-Wide Plan, Undated (Box 79, Folder 7)
  - Student Association, 1989 (Box 79, Folder 8)
  - Student Association, 1988 (Box 79, Folder 9)
  - Teacher Evaluation, Undated (Box 79, Folder 10)
  - "Truth in Testing", Undated (Box 79, Folder 11)
  - Undergraduate studies, 1989 (Box 79, Folder 12)
  - Undergraduate studies, 1988 (Box 79, Folder 13)
  - U.A.S. University Building Committee, Undated (Box 79, Folder 14)
  - University Foundation, 1988 (Box 79, Folder 15)
  - University Foundation: Capital Partnership, Undated (Box 79, Folder 16)
  - University at Albany Fund, 1989 (Box 79, Folder 17)
  - University at Albany Fund, 1988 (Box 79, Folder 18)
  - university Relations, 1988 (Box 79, Folder 19)
  - Gordimer Reception, Undated (Box 79, Folder 20)
  - Writers Institute, 1989 (Box 79, Folder 21)
  - Writers Institute, 1988 (Box 79, Folder 22)
  - Norman Mailer Reception, Undated (Box 79, Folder 23)
  - Styron Reception, Undated (Box 79, Folder 24)
  - Vice Presidents Meeting- Minutes, 1989 (Box 80, Folder 1)
  - Vice Presidents Meeting- Minutes, 1988 (Box 80, Folder 2)
  - Vice Presidents Meeting, 1986 (Box 80, Folder 3)